Guide to the Bill Andrews Editorial Cartoons and Papers GRAPHICS.038
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Artwork by Others
  Contains artwork given to Andrews by other artists, including friends such as Homer Kellogg, Marcia Yutman and Marilyn and Charles Trussell as well as professional cartoonists, including Kearny Egerton, Bil Keane and Gee Tee Maxwell, whom Andrews befriended while working at the Arizona Republic. Also included is artwork sent to Andrews while he worked at the Daily World from individuals seeking to have their work published in the paper.
  - Anonemous (sic) ("Mister Little and Mister Big"), undated (Box 42, Folder 637)
  - Chapin, ?, undated (Box 42, Folder 638)
  - Davis, Jack, undated (Box 42, Folder 639)
  - Egerton, Kearney, 1952, undated (Box 42, Folder 640)
  - Foley, Tom, May 1976 (Box 42, Folder 641)
  - Harman, Fred, undated (Box 42, Folder 677)
  - Joseph, Seymour, Sep 25, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 642)
  - Keane, Bil, 1958, undated (Box 42, Folder 643)
  - Kellogg, Homer, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 644)
  - Kennedy, Joe, undated (Box 42, Folder 645)
  - Manning, Reg, 1950, undated (Box 42, Folder 646)
  - Newcomb, Ken, 1963-1964 (Box 42, Folder 647)
  - Osmolski, Joe, May 1966 (Box 42, Folder 648)
  - Trussell, Charles, undated (Box 42, Folder 649)
  - Trussell, Marilyn, undated (Box 42, Folder 650)
  - Unidentified Artwork, undated (Box 42, Folder 651)
  - Yutman, Marcia, undated (Box 42, Folder 652)